Contact

lilly.rowe91@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lillyannrowe (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Acute Care ICU

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Spanish (Elementary)
Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Stem Cell Transplant Certificate
Basic Life Support for Healthcare
Providers (BLS)

Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support (ACLS)

Assaultive Behavior Management Hospital Fire and Life Safety

Lillyann Rowe, BSN, RN, CCRN, CPAN, PHN

Registered Nurse at Cedars-Sinai Medical Center & Kaiser Permanente

Greater Los Angeles Area

Summary

Experienced, Dual-Board Certified Registered Nurse with specialization as both a Critical Care Registered Nurse (CCRN) and Certified Peri-Anesthesia Nurse (CPAN)

Current BSN to MSN student at Western Governors University with an anticipated graduation year of 2022.

Experience

Cedars-Sinai 5 years 3 months

Clinical Nurse III (Pre-Op/PACU)
September 2016 - Present (3 years 10 months)
Beverly Hills, California

7 Main Pre-Op/PACU

Inpatient and outpatient Post-Anesthesia Care Unit (PACU) & Pre-Op: Colorectals, General Surgery, Orthopedics/Traumas, Urology, and OB Gynecology

PACU Charge Nurse, Relief Nurse, Pre-Op Team Lead, Relief PACU Triage Nurse, New PACU RN preceptor, Magnet Committee Chair, MD/RN Committee Chair, Port Champion

Employee of the Quarter Award Recipient, Awarded multiple Standing Ovations, Unit TOTI Award Winners, Safety Star Award Recipient

Clinical Nurse III (ICU)
April 2020 - May 2020 (2 months)
Beverly Hills, California, United States

ICU Float Nurse: 5-SCCT (Surgical), 7-SCCT (Medical/Respiratory), 8-SCCT (Neuro)

Temporary in-hospital deployment to assist with possible influx of COVID-19 patients in the Intensive Care Unit

Clinical Nurse II & III (Hem/Onc) April 2015 - September 2016 (1 year 6 months) Beverly Hills, California

4-SE: Hematology/Oncology/Chemotherapy

End-Of-Life Care & Hospice

Medical overflow

Charge Nurse & Student/New Grad Preceptor, Chemotherapy Certified, Bone Marrow Transplant Certified, EKG Champion

Kaiser Permanente Registered Nurse August 2019 - Present (11 months) Baldwin Park, California

Pre-Op & Post-Anesthesia (PACU) Irwindale Outpatient Surgery Center Ambulatory Surgical Unit (ASU)

General Surgery, Eyes/Cataracts, Outpatient Orthopedics, Urology

UCLA Health Resource Nurse May 2017 - November 2017 (7 months) Santa Monica, California

Intensive Care Unit (ICU) Float Nurse Pre-Op/Post-Anesthesia (PACU) Float Nurse

San Gabriel Valley Medical Center 2 years 9 months

Registered Nurse (ICU) March 2016 - April 2017 (1 year 2 months) San Gabriel, California

Intensive Care Unit (ICU)

Registered Nurse (Surgical) August 2014 - March 2016 (1 year 8 months) San Gabriel, California Tower 4 (T4): Surgical Pre/Post-Op, Chemotherapy, Inpatient Hospice, Medical Overflow

New RN Preceptor, Nursing Student Preceptor

Southern California Hospitals Registered Nurse October 2013 - September 2014 (1 year) Hollywood, California

Formerly Known As: "Alta Hospitals System, LLC: Hollywood Community Hospital"

New Graduate Registered Nurse: Medical-Surgical Telemetry
Float Nurse: Step-down (DOU), Intensive Care Unit (ICU), and Urgent Care/
Emergency

New RN Preceptor, Nursing Student Preceptor

Pacific Alliance Medical Center Certified Nursing Assistant September 2012 - September 2013 (1 year 1 month) Los Angeles, California

Medical-Surgical Telemetry Unit CNA
Direct Patient Care

San Gabriel Health Clinic
Medical Office Assistant
June 2011 - January 2013 (1 year 8 months)

Rosemead, California

Primary Care Physician Offices of: Dr. Bo Huynh and Dr. Christine Dinh

Front Desk, Vital Signs/Intake, Specimen/Lab Preparation, Filing

Education

Western Governors University

Master of Science - MS, Nursing Leadership and Management · (2020 - 2022)

West Coast University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2010 - 2013)

Rio Hondo College

General Education, Pre-Nursing Studies · (2009 - 2010)

Los Angeles County ROP

Certified Nurse Assistant, Nursing Assistant Certification · (2010 - 2010)

Rosemead High School

High School Diploma, High School/Secondary Diplomas and Certificates · (2005 - 2009)